[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Is that really true, or is this like every other presidential race?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "really", "true", ",", "or", "is", "this", "like", "every", "other", "presidential", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "No, this is not like every other presidential race.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "this", "is", "not", "like", "every", "other", "presidential", "race", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Which side do you sit on?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "side", "do", "you", "sit", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, this is true that Barack Obama has been much more cautious, much more willing to compromise and cut what seemed to be his principles.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "true", "that", "Barack", "Obama", "has", "been", "much", "more", "cautious", ",", "much", "more", "willing", "to", "compromise", "and", "cut", "what", "seemed", "to", "be", "his", "principles", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "But this has been such a topsy-turvy nomination process on the Republican side that who knows how it's going to turn out?", "question_tokens": ["But", "this", "has", "been", "such", "a", "topsy-turvy", "nomination", "process", "on", "the", "Republican", "side", "that", "who", "knows", "how", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "turn", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "WP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "And I think there's something about Rick Santorum's demeanor at the moment that makes me think, having interviewed him a few times now, he believes he's got a chance, and the reason, I think, is that he suspects that the party isn't as in love with Mitt Romney as it should be, and that they are looking really for a more traditional conservative and the religious aspect, I think, is significant, too.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "something", "about", "Rick", "Santorum", "'s", "demeanor", "at", "the", "moment", "that", "makes", "me", "think", ",", "having", "interviewed", "him", "a", "few", "times", "now", ",", "he", "believes", "he", "'s", "got", "a", "chance", ",", "and", "the", "reason", ",", "I", "think", ",", "is", "that", "he", "suspects", "that", "the", "party", "is", "n't", "as", "in", "love", "with", "Mitt", "Romney", "as", "it", "should", "be", ",", "and", "that", "they", "are", "looking", "really", "for", "a", "more", "traditional", "conservative", "and", "the", "religious", "aspect", ",", "I", "think", ",", "is", "significant", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Syria"]}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBZ", ",", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "What do you think America should be doing right now about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "America", "should", "be", "doing", "right", "now", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, it's a real Rubik's cube that what I think America should be doing, not that anybody should care, is, one, it should be increasing the pressure at all ways and anyways possible for diplomatic pressure, for sanctions, for the freezing of assets, the banning of travel, and making it so far as possible Syria an international pariah.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "real", "Rubik", "'s", "cube", "that", "what", "I", "think", "America", "should", "be", "doing", ",", "not", "that", "anybody", "should", "care", ",", "is", ",", "one", ",", "it", "should", "be", "increasing", "the", "pressure", "at", "all", "ways", "and", "anyways", "possible", "for", "diplomatic", "pressure", ",", "for", "sanctions", ",", "for", "the", "freezing", "of", "assets", ",", "the", "banning", "of", "travel", ",", "and", "making", "it", "so", "far", "as", "possible", "Syria", "an", "international", "pariah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Russia", "China"]}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "What should America do in relation to those two countries and the position they've taken?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "America", "do", "in", "relation", "to", "those", "two", "countries", "and", "the", "position", "they", "'ve", "taken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Well, two different countries, Russia and China.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "two", "different", "countries", ",", "Russia", "and", "China", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What do you make of what is happening in relation to the first lady popping up now and offering her support in this way?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "is", "happening", "in", "relation", "to", "the", "first", "lady", "popping", "up", "now", "and", "offering", "her", "support", "in", "this", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "It seems incongruous, Piers, and off the mark and the statement doesn't make much sense.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "seems", "incongruous", ",", "Piers", ",", "and", "off", "the", "mark", "and", "the", "statement", "does", "n't", "make", "much", "sense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Acton"]}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJS", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "When you interviewed her, but when you interviewed her, what sense did you get about her as a woman and her place in the Syrian hierarchy?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "interviewed", "her", ",", "but", "when", "you", "interviewed", "her", ",", "what", "sense", "did", "you", "get", "about", "her", "as", "a", "woman", "and", "her", "place", "in", "the", "Syrian", "hierarchy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "What was most interesting is that she was born in Acton.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "was", "most", "interesting", "is", "that", "she", "was", "born", "in", "Acton", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "What was your take on him personally?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "take", "on", "him", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "What was kind of an inadvertent because I didn't really want to do the piece in the first place because I didn't really want to meet the Assads or go to Syria but when I went she said that she was going to cook lunch for me.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "was", "kind", "of", "an", "inadvertent", "because", "I", "did", "n't", "really", "want", "to", "do", "the", "piece", "in", "the", "first", "place", "because", "I", "did", "n't", "really", "want", "to", "meet", "the", "Assads", "or", "go", "to", "Syria", "but", "when", "I", "went", "she", "said", "that", "she", "was", "going", "to", "cook", "lunch", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Do you think the Assads can just bat this will out or do you believe that international pressure in the end will lead to them being overthrown?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "Assads", "can", "just", "bat", "this", "will", "out", "or", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "international", "pressure", "in", "the", "end", "will", "lead", "to", "them", "being", "overthrown", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "You know, I'm not a political journalist.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "political", "journalist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "What is it that you want to bring to the political system that maybe isn't there at the moment in enough quantity?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "that", "you", "want", "to", "bring", "to", "the", "political", "system", "that", "maybe", "is", "n't", "there", "at", "the", "moment", "in", "enough", "quantity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well, I really feel very strongly that the tone of our political discourse has gotten way out of control.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "really", "feel", "very", "strongly", "that", "the", "tone", "of", "our", "political", "discourse", "has", "gotten", "way", "out", "of", "control", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What advice has Gabby Giffords given you about the challenge now facing you in a potential election?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "has", "Gabby", "Giffords", "given", "you", "about", "the", "challenge", "now", "facing", "you", "in", "a", "potential", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "I have just lost my microphone or earpiece.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "just", "lost", "my", "microphone", "or", "earpiece", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gabby Giffords"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "How much of that is really him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "that", "is", "really", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I think that also comes from a place of honesty.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "also", "comes", "from", "a", "place", "of", "honesty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Be honest, have you ever had a word with him about his hair?", "question_tokens": ["Be", "honest", ",", "have", "you", "ever", "had", "a", "word", "with", "him", "about", "his", "hair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "No, I haven't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Too many other people have, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Too", "many", "other", "people", "have", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I quite like it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "quite", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "So you think Bieber's basically taking the Donald look?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "think", "Bieber", "'s", "basically", "taking", "the", "Donald", "look", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Oh, yeah, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bieber", "Donald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Are you seeing the same green chutes that others are beginning to see?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "seeing", "the", "same", "green", "chutes", "that", "others", "are", "beginning", "to", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "I think now, for us, it's a really exciting time, because now we're really looking at the opportunity to buy assets, to buy assets that in many cases, you know, could use a lot of enhancements, that were half built.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "now", ",", "for", "us", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "really", "exciting", "time", ",", "because", "now", "we", "'re", "really", "looking", "at", "the", "opportunity", "to", "buy", "assets", ",", "to", "buy", "assets", "that", "in", "many", "cases", ",", "you", "know", ",", "could", "use", "a", "lot", "of", "enhancements", ",", "that", "were", "half", "built", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Are you as looking forward to another four years of Barack Obama, as your father clearly is?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "as", "looking", "forward", "to", "another", "four", "years", "of", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "as", "your", "father", "clearly", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Let's hope not.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "hope", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Are you a die hard Republican?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "die", "hard", "Republican", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "I am -- I am vehemently against most of Obama's policies.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "--", "I", "am", "vehemently", "against", "most", "of", "Obama", "'s", "policies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Do you guys have a goal in terms of fund-raising?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "guys", "have", "a", "goal", "in", "terms", "of", "fund-raising", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: Yeah, we do.", "answer_tokens": ["NIDENTIFIED", "MALE", ":", "Yeah", ",", "we", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJS", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "At least five.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "least", "five", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "But for you, who has this incredible business going everywhere else, how often do you think, I really want to be in Dubai now?", "question_tokens": ["But", "for", "you", ",", "who", "has", "this", "incredible", "business", "going", "everywhere", "else", ",", "how", "often", "do", "you", "think", ",", "I", "really", "want", "to", "be", "in", "Dubai", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "You know, it's interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dubai"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Now how is motherhood going?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "how", "is", "motherhood", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "It's incredible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "incredible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Where is the Ivanka Trump video for how to get back in shape after a baby coming out?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "the", "Ivanka", "Trump", "video", "for", "how", "to", "get", "back", "in", "shape", "after", "a", "baby", "coming", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I thought you were going to ask about a line of baby apparel.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "you", "were", "going", "to", "ask", "about", "a", "line", "of", "baby", "apparel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ivanka Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "But are you enjoying it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "are", "you", "enjoying", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "RUMP: I love it.", "answer_tokens": ["RUMP", ":", "I", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How is Grandfather Donald getting on?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "Grandfather", "Donald", "getting", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "-- so much fun.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "so", "much", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "No diaper changing, right?", "question_tokens": ["No", "diaper", "changing", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Zero.", "answer_tokens": ["Zero", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Which is shocking, because he's very hands on.", "answer_tokens": ["Which", "is", "shocking", ",", "because", "he", "'s", "very", "hands", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "How did I know this would come back to haunt me?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "I", "know", "this", "would", "come", "back", "to", "haunt", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I loved that moment.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "loved", "that", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]